

Gabriel Cornejo

Web Developer



7 mar, 2001



https://github.com/GabrielCornejoB



+57 316 356 6865



gabrielcorbot@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

Web developer on his 3rd year of Systems and Computer Engineering, has experience working in web development and data analytics.

Great leadership and team-working habilities, adapts easily to different roles and environments, besides that, very apassionate to coding, learning new technologies and working in great teams with great people.

CAREER

MAY 2022 - SEPT 2022 IT CONSULTANT

UPB -Gobernación de Antioquia

Here I developed Web Applications and Python scripts to give support to processes and activities of a Data Governance Consultancy for "Gobernación de Antioquia"

OCT 2021 - ABR 2022

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

GIA UPB

I realized activities based on Data Analysis and Data Collection using tools like Python, PowerBI and Excel, this to help a Research about CO2 pollution generated by vehicles in "Valle de Aburrá"

LANGUAGES

SPANISH/ ENGLISH

EDUCATION

ENE 2020 -NOW

UNIVERSIDAD PONTIFICIA BOLIVARIANA

Bachelor in Systems and Computer Engineering

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML JavaScript Python Angular MongoDB Java Node.js CSS/SASS **TypeScript** Postgres